<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>This Is Hypocrisy</title>
    <description>This Is Hypocrisy archives every instance of hypocrisy from the mainstream media. Many media companies stretch and bend reality to spin a story, and sometimes they get caught. To keep them accountable, we plan to archive every instance of hypocrisy to understand the extent of the deception. 
</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 20:22:00 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 20:22:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Media Claims Trump Has No Plan To Reach 3% GDP Growth - and We Just Reached 4.1% GDP Growth</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Since 2010, US’s GDP growth has stagnated at around 2%. Donald Trump set a 3% annual GDP growth goal. As expected, the media has assumed a highly critical position. Here are some examples:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.latimes.com/business/hiltzik/la-fi-3percent-20170519-story.html&quot;&gt;“If Trump thinks he can get more than 3% economic growth, he’s dreaming”&lt;/a&gt; - Michael Hiltzik, Los Angeles Times&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/labor-force-stands-in-way-of-trumps-3-growth-goal-1494861153&quot;&gt;“Can Trump Deliver 3% Growth? Stubborn Realities Stand in the Way”&lt;/a&gt; - Nick Timiraos and Andrew Tangel, The Wall Street Journal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/sorry-mr-trump-the-only-way-to-get-to-3-growth-is-to-hire-more-mexicans-2016-12-05&quot;&gt;“Sorry, Mr. Trump, but the only way to get to 3% growth is to hire more Mexicans”&lt;/a&gt; - Rex Nutting, MarketWatch&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://money.cnn.com/2016/10/11/news/economy/trump-four-percent-growth-economists/index.html&quot;&gt;“Trump promises 4% growth. Economists say no way.”&lt;/a&gt; - Patrick Gillespie, CNN Money&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2017/07/14/537263663/why-maganomics-isnt-likely-to-work&quot;&gt;“Why ‘MAGAnomics’ Isn’t Likely To Work”&lt;/a&gt; - Danielle Kurtzleben, NPR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, unfortunately for the media, the US is well on it’s way to reach the 3% goal. In Q2 of 2018, GDP growth reached a spectacular 4.1%, the highest quarterly GDP growth rate in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-27/u-s-gdp-growth-hits-4-1-fastest-since-2014-in-win-for-trump&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/nPZsC1l.jpg&quot; class=&quot;-fullwidth -outline&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 19:35:30 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/posts/the-media-claims-trump-has-no-plan-to-3-gdp-growth/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/the-media-claims-trump-has-no-plan-to-3-gdp-growth/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Newsweek Implies That Donald Trump Is Anti-Semitic - Yet They Forget...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;… that Trump is one of the most pro-Israel presidents we’ve had in recent times. Trump, for one, was the first president to actually relocate the US embassy from Tel Aviv to Jerusalem since the Jerusalem Embassy Act of 1995 became law. Despite the act becoming law, Clinton, Bush, and Obama repeatedly invoked a six-month waiver of the application of the law (which includes the relocation of the US embassy to Jerusalem).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, the Israeli ambassador to the United States, Ron Dermer, said on July 23rd, 2018, has this to say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“There has never been a U.S. administration more supportive of Israel than the Trump administration. Frankly, it is not even close. …This is an administration that sees Israel as an ally and that treats Israel as an ally. Today, the alliance between Israel and America has never been stronger.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite this, Newsweek ran an article implying that Donald Trump is anti-Semitic because he used the word “globalist”. I’m surprised the term “globalist” is even anti-Semitic. Is “globalisation” an anti-Semitic concept? At this point, many reporters seem to be grasping at straws to paint Donald Trump as the racist, white supremacist, anti-Semitic, xenophobic, hateful, anti-LGBTQIA, misogynistic, incompetent president.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/DukfYqq.jpg&quot; class=&quot;-tweet -outline&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/scHaGyT.jpg&quot; class=&quot;-tweet -outline&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 19:12:44 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/posts/newsweek-implies-that-donald-trump-is-antisemitic-yet-they-forget/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/newsweek-implies-that-donald-trump-is-antisemitic-yet-they-forget/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Media Misleads Public on Trump's Fish-Feeding Technique in a PR Event With the Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In November last year, a story came out that Donald Trump, while in a fish-feeding PR event with the Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe in the Akasaka Palace, was impatient and ignorant of foreign customs and dumped an entire box of fish food into the pond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few examples:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Trump and Abe spooning fish food into a pond. (Toward the end, @potus decided to just dump the whole box in for the fish)” - &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/justinsink/status/927372928227819521&quot;&gt;Justin Sink, Bloomberg’s White House reporter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Big stupid baby dumps a load of fish food on Japanese koi pond” - &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Jezebel/status/927490456237301760&quot;&gt;Jezebel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“Trump and Japanese PM Shinzo Abe were scheduled to feed koi spoonfuls of food. Until Trump poured his entire box of fish food into the pond.” - CNBC’s Christina Wilkie (deleted tweet)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“White House reporters, keen perhaps to pick up on a Trump gaffe, captured the moment when he upended his box on their smartphones and tweeted evidence of his questionable grasp of fish keeping. Some speculated that a poor palace employee would be dispatched to the scene to clean up the mess as soon as the two leaders disappeared inside.” - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2017/nov/06/trump-dump-president-throws-entire-box-of-fish-food-into-precious-koi-carp-pond&quot;&gt;The Guardian&lt;/a&gt; (this article was later corrected)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;“President Trump feeds fish with PM Shinzo Abe in Japan, then pours the entire box of food into the koi pond.” - &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/VeronicaRochaLA/status/927400669996130305&quot;&gt;CNN’s Veronica Rocha&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/nJluWFQ.jpg&quot; class=&quot;-outline -tweet&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem is, Trump wasn’t the only one who poured his entire box of fish food into the pond. Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe actually did it first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scary thing is, CNN’s tweet actually contained a video that purposely edited out Abe so viewers would not see that Trump was actually following Abe’s lead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/KczHVwX.jpg&quot; class=&quot;-fullwidth&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 16:41:06 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/posts/the-media-misleads-public-on-trumps-fish-feeding-technique/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/the-media-misleads-public-on-trumps-fish-feeding-technique/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Clintons's Pivotal Role In The Sale Of Uranium One To Russia - Yet Donald Trump Is the Russian Puppet</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The mainstream media loves to suggest that Donald Trump is controlled by the Russian government, even in the absence of concrete proof. They spin any small connection between the Trump family and a Russian entity as a possibility that Trump is a Russian puppet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some examples:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2018/07/trump-putin-russia-collusion.html&quot;&gt;“Will Trump Be Meeting With His Counterpart — Or His Handler?”&lt;/a&gt; - Daily Intelligencer, July 2018&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/follow-the-russian-money-and-tighten-your-seatbelt/2018/08/03/a0397c40-967f-11e8-a679-b09212fb69c2_story.html?noredirect=on&amp;amp;utm_term=.86c8432e45cb&quot;&gt;“Follow the Russian money, and tighten your seatbelt”&lt;/a&gt; - The Washington Post, August 2018&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://newrepublic.com/article/143586/trumps-russian-laundromat-trump-tower-luxury-high-rises-dirty-money-international-crime-syndicate&quot;&gt;“Trump’s Russian Laundromat”&lt;/a&gt; - The New Republic, July 2017&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-patterson-trump-russia-collusion_us_5b72400be4b0bdd0620c350f&quot;&gt;“The Trump-Russia Facts Lead To Only One Reasonable Conclusion”&lt;/a&gt; - HuffPost, August 2018&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/trump-acting-like-russian-asset-experts-say-2018-7&quot;&gt;“National security experts warn Trump is behaving more and more like a ‘controlled spy’”&lt;/a&gt; - Business Insider, July 2018&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnn.com/interactive/2017/politics/trump-russia-connections/&quot;&gt;“The many paths from Trump to Russia”&lt;/a&gt;, December 2017&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;And thousands more of articles with similar themes from “esteemed” media organizations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, talk about a conspiracy theory. The mainstream media loves to label theories they disagree with as conspiracy theories, yet when it’s something they want to happen, they embrace a conspiracy theory with open arms. There is no concrete proof (emphasis on “concrete”) that Trump is a Russian asset. If one tries hard enough, one can draw Russian connections to every billionaire in the world. It’s a globalized world. If Trump was actually a Russian asset, it doesn’t require journalists to dig around to discover evidence, he would immediately be outed by any of the country’s intelligence agencies that have tens of billions of dollars in annual funding. Trump has been in office for almost 2 years. If the Russian government had an exploitative relationship with Trump, it would have been discovered by now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In any case, it’s interesting that amid all this frenzy with Trump-Russia connections, the “objective” media has been eerily silent about the Clinton family’s connections with Russia. One standout example is Bill Clinton’s 2010 speech in Moscow to a Russian investment bank, Renaissance Capital. Clinton received $500,000 from the bank for the speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Rosatom, Russia’s nuclear energy agency, had recently announced their intention to acquire a majority stake in Uranium One, a Canadian company responsible for 20% of the US’s uranium mining output. Coincidentally, Renaissance Capital started promoting Uranium One stock during this time and, in a July 2010 research report, claimed that the company’s stock was “the best play” in the uranium markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hillary Clinton was Secretary of State during this time and she approved the sale of Uranium One to Rosatom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s also interesting to note that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.politico.com/story/2017/11/14/hillary-clinton-uranium-one-deal-russia-explainer-244895&quot;&gt;“several of Uranium One’s owners were also donors to the Clinton Foundation, giving $145 million to the charitable foundation”&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 15:48:13 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/posts/the-clintons-pivotal-role-uranium-one/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/the-clintons-pivotal-role-uranium-one/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Newsweek Contradicts Itself on the South African White Farmers Situation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s widely known that the South African government is seizing land without fair compensation from the nation’s white-owned farms. In March 1st, 2018, Quartz Africa published this article, &lt;a href=&quot;https://qz.com/africa/1218309/south-africa-to-take-land-without-compensation-as-zimbabwe-backtracks-on-seizing-white-farms/&quot;&gt;“Expropriating land without compensation is impossible - take it from Zimbabwe”&lt;/a&gt;. On August 21st, 2018, news.com.au released this article, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.news.com.au/finance/economy/world-economy/south-africa-begins-seizing-whiteowned-farms/news-story/8937f899bd3f131bfc4ffb648ea5c53b&quot;&gt;“South Africa begins seizing white-owned farms”&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to this news, Trump tweeted:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I have asked Secretary of State @SecPompeo to closely study the South Africa land and farm seizures and expropriations and the large scale killing of farmers. “South African Government is now seizing land from white farmers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mainstreaming media immediately pounced on Trump’s tweet by claiming that this narrative is perpertrated by “white supremacists”. First of all, it’s unfortunate that the media loves to arbitrarily give hateful labels like “white supremacist” and “racist” to anyone they disagree with. Often times, there is no concrete proof or data that these people are actually white supremacists or racists and there is a huge cost to anyone being labeled as such. These labels should NOT be thrown around lightly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the media organizations that responded to Trump’s tweet is Newsweek. They recently published an article titled &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newsweek.com/white-nationalists-trump-south-african-farmers-1087549&quot;&gt;“WHITE NATIONALISTS PRAISE DONALD TRUMP FOR SPREADING WHITE SOUTH AFRICAN FARMERS CONSPIRACY THEORY”&lt;/a&gt;. Unfortunately, it’s quite hypocritical of Newsweek to claim Donald Trump is spreading this “conspiracy theory” when they themsleves published an article on March 19th titled &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newsweek.com/white-farmer-killed-every-five-days-south-africa-authorities-do-nothing-851470&quot;&gt;“A WHITE FARMER IS KILLED EVERY FIVE DAYS IN SOUTH AFRICA AND AUTHORITIES DO NOTHING ABOUT IT, ACTIVISTS SAY”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/5sJabyi.jpg&quot; class=&quot;-outline -tweet&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 15:18:17 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/posts/newsweek-contradicts-itself-on-the-south-african-white-farmers-situation/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/newsweek-contradicts-itself-on-the-south-african-white-farmers-situation/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MeToo Leader Rose McGowan's Double Standards</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Rose McGowan is  one of the leaders of the MeToo movement. On November 17th, 2017, she &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/rosemcgowan/status/931338274542460928?lang=en&quot;&gt;tweeted&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It’s quite simple, all who have worked with known predators should do 3 simple things. 1) Believe survivors 2) Apologize for putting your careers and wallets before what was right 3) Grab a spine and denounce. If you do not do these things you are still moral cowards. #ROSEARMY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/srfV53x.jpg&quot; class=&quot;-outline -tweet&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a bombshell report revealed that Asia Argento agreed to pay $380,000 to an actor who accused her of sexually assaulting him when he was 17 years old, she tweet:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;None of us know the truth of the situation and I’m sure more will be revealed. Be gentle,” she added, sparking condemnations and accusations of hypocrisy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/q3kOLfx.jpg&quot; class=&quot;-outline -tweet&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her double standards are clear here. For her friends, they deserve to be innocent until proven guilty. For others, they are guilty until proven innocent. Beyond this incident, it’s crazy that she, and the rest of the MeToo movement, actually believes guilty until proven innocent is civil and moral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McGowan has since deleted the tweet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 14:44:21 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/posts/metoo-leader-rose-mcgowans-double-standards/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/metoo-leader-rose-mcgowans-double-standards/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NBC, Amazon, And Cartoon Network Writer Asks For White Extinction</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On June 25th, Taylor Cox, a writer for many children’s TV shows including Just Add Magic, Swamp Talk with Shrek &amp;amp; Donkey, OMG!, and Kung Fu Panda tweeted this statement: “the only anxiety i have about white Extinction is that it’s not happening fast enough”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cox has since deleted the tweet and took her Twitter account private.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a progressive, it’s surprising that she has convinced herself that it’s okay to publicly ask for the extinction of an entire human race. I guess, when your need to virtue signal overcomes critical thinking, this is the result.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Sf7TD0h.jpg&quot; class=&quot;-outline -fullwidth&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 04:04:32 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/posts/nbc-amazon-and-cartoon-network-writer-asks-for-white-extinction/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/posts/nbc-amazon-and-cartoon-network-writer-asks-for-white-extinction/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
